[
  {
    "source":"mp3/BlueMonday.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "New Order",
    "choice2": "Joy Division",
    "choice3": "The Cure",
    "choice4": "Pet Shop Boys",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/DontGo.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Erasure",
    "choice2": "Yazoo",
    "choice3": "Kraftwerk",
    "choice4": "Ultravox",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/DontStopBelievin.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Odyssey",
    "choice2": "Foreigner",
    "choice3": "Journey",
    "choice4": "Toto",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/DontYou.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Tears for Fears",
    "choice2": "The Smiths",
    "choice3": "The Pretenders",
    "choice4": "Simple Minds",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/DontYouWantMe.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Spandau Ballet",
    "choice2": "The Human League",
    "choice3": "Soft Cell",
    "choice4": "ABC",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/ElectricAvenue.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Billy Ocean",
    "choice2": "Icehouse",
    "choice3": "Eddy Grant",
    "choice4": "Alphaville",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/EnolaGay.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "XTC",
    "choice2": "OMG",
    "choice3": "OTT",
    "choice4": "OMD",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/JustCantGetEnough.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Depeche Mode",
    "choice2": "Johnny Hates Jazz",
    "choice3": "Talk Talk",
    "choice4": "Culture Club",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Material Girl.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Kim Wilde",
    "choice2": "Madonna",
    "choice3": "Samantha Fox",
    "choice4": "Cyndi Lauper",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/NeedYouTonight.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Duran Duran",
    "choice2": "Tears for Fears",
    "choice3": "INXS",
    "choice4": "Bronski Beat",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/NeverGonnaGiveYou Up.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Jason Donovan",
    "choice2": "George Michael",
    "choice3": "Donny Osmond",
    "choice4": "Rick Astley",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/SheDrivesMeCrazy.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Fine Young Cannibals",
    "choice2": "Bronski Beat",
    "choice3": "The Communards",
    "choice4": "Frankie Goes to Hollywood",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/WalkLikeanEgyptian.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Bananarama",
    "choice2": "The Bangles",
    "choice3": "The Go-Go's",
    "choice4": "The Runaways",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Youspinmeround.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Yazz",
    "choice2": "The Spinners",
    "choice3": "Dead or Alive",
    "choice4": "Re-Flex",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/SweetDreams.mp3",
    "question": "Who's singing this song?",
    "choice1": "Roxette",
    "choice2": "Kajagoogoo",
    "choice3": "Propaganda",
    "choice4": "Eurythmics",
    "answer": 4
  }
]